{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947300176698","data":{"timestamp":" 947300176698"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000108_055559"," gameId":" 9351deb8-626e-4326-8abd-df7714ccd7eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_A-E-M"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947300182088","data":{"timestamp":" 947300182087"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000108_055559"," gameId":" 9351deb8-626e-4326-8abd-df7714ccd7eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_U-P-M"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947300186426","data":{"timestamp":" 947300186426"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000108_055559"," gameId":" 9351deb8-626e-4326-8abd-df7714ccd7eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_U-M-Y"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947300191884","data":{"timestamp":" 947300191884"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000108_055559"," gameId":" 9351deb8-626e-4326-8abd-df7714ccd7eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_L-M-Z"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947300195112","data":{"timestamp":" 947300195112"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000108_055559"," gameId":" 9351deb8-626e-4326-8abd-df7714ccd7eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_M_L-M-Z"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947300207257","data":{"timestamp":" 947300207257"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000108_055559"," gameId":" e5f943a8-c404-4ab0-8b1d-068ae731e40d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliondokea mvulana mmoja aliyeitwa Demane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947300207842","data":{"timestamp":" 947300207842"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000108_055559"," gameId":" e5f943a8-c404-4ab0-8b1d-068ae731e40d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliondokea mvulana mmoja aliyeitwa Demane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947300208035","data":{"timestamp":" 947300208035"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000108_055559"," gameId":" e5f943a8-c404-4ab0-8b1d-068ae731e40d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliondokea mvulana mmoja aliyeitwa Demane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947300208419","data":{"timestamp":" 947300208419"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000108_055559"," gameId":" e5f943a8-c404-4ab0-8b1d-068ae731e40d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliondokea mvulana mmoja aliyeitwa Demane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947300209892","data":{"timestamp":" 947300209891"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000108_055559"," gameId":" e5f943a8-c404-4ab0-8b1d-068ae731e40d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliondokea mvulana mmoja aliyeitwa Demane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIONDOKEA"," userResponse":" PALIONDOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947300210544","data":{"timestamp":" 947300210544"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000108_055559"," gameId":" e5f943a8-c404-4ab0-8b1d-068ae731e40d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliondokea mvulana mmoja aliyeitwa Demane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVULANA"," userResponse":" MVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947300211317","data":{"timestamp":" 947300211317"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000108_055559"," gameId":" e5f943a8-c404-4ab0-8b1d-068ae731e40d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliondokea mvulana mmoja aliyeitwa Demane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947300212410","data":{"timestamp":" 947300212410"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000108_055559"," gameId":" e5f943a8-c404-4ab0-8b1d-068ae731e40d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliondokea mvulana mmoja aliyeitwa Demane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEITWA"," userResponse":" ALIYEITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947300213093","data":{"timestamp":" 947300213093"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000108_055559"," gameId":" e5f943a8-c404-4ab0-8b1d-068ae731e40d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliondokea mvulana mmoja aliyeitwa Demane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DEMANE"," userResponse":" DEMANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947300215514","data":{"timestamp":" 947300215513"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000108_055559"," gameId":" e5f943a8-c404-4ab0-8b1d-068ae731e40d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947300215736","data":{"timestamp":" 947300215736"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000108_055559"," gameId":" e5f943a8-c404-4ab0-8b1d-068ae731e40d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947300216179","data":{"timestamp":" 947300216179"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000108_055559"," gameId":" e5f943a8-c404-4ab0-8b1d-068ae731e40d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PACHA"," userResponse":" PACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947300217022","data":{"timestamp":" 947300217022"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000108_055559"," gameId":" e5f943a8-c404-4ab0-8b1d-068ae731e40d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENZAKE"," userResponse":" MWENZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947300218215","data":{"timestamp":" 947300218215"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000108_055559"," gameId":" e5f943a8-c404-4ab0-8b1d-068ae731e40d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEITWA"," userResponse":" ALIYEITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947300219128","data":{"timestamp":" 947300219128"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000108_055559"," gameId":" e5f943a8-c404-4ab0-8b1d-068ae731e40d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DEMAZANE"," userResponse":" DEMAZANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947300228939","data":{"timestamp":" 947300228939"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000108_055559"," gameId":" e5f943a8-c404-4ab0-8b1d-068ae731e40d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947300229000","data":{"timestamp":" 947300229000"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000108_055559"," gameId":" e5f943a8-c404-4ab0-8b1d-068ae731e40d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DEMAZANE"," userResponse":" DEMAZANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947300237043","data":{"timestamp":" 947300237042"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000108_055559"," gameId":" e5f943a8-c404-4ab0-8b1d-068ae731e40d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947300248960","data":{"timestamp":" 947300248960"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000108_055559"," gameId":" 76d41e81-9fa1-43f3-939f-418c556774df"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_7-8-6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947300257236","data":{"timestamp":" 947300257236"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000108_055559"," gameId":" 76d41e81-9fa1-43f3-939f-418c556774df"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_1-3-2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947300262937","data":{"timestamp":" 947300262937"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000108_055559"," gameId":" 76d41e81-9fa1-43f3-939f-418c556774df"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_1-3-2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947300320440","data":{"timestamp":" 947300320440"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000108_055559"," gameId":" 76d41e81-9fa1-43f3-939f-418c556774df"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-6-5"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947300326008","data":{"timestamp":" 947300326008"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000108_055559"," gameId":" 76d41e81-9fa1-43f3-939f-418c556774df"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-6-5"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947300331434","data":{"timestamp":" 947300331433"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000108_055559"," gameId":" 76d41e81-9fa1-43f3-939f-418c556774df"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-6-5"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947300333845","data":{"timestamp":" 947300333844"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000108_055559"," gameId":" 76d41e81-9fa1-43f3-939f-418c556774df"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-6-5"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947300342900","data":{"timestamp":" 947300342899"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000108_055559"," gameId":" b55266b1-bae7-44db-b999-f66a2f3fb589"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-R-H"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947300346965","data":{"timestamp":" 947300346965"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000108_055559"," gameId":" b55266b1-bae7-44db-b999-f66a2f3fb589"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_P-B-R"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947300351982","data":{"timestamp":" 947300351982"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000108_055559"," gameId":" b55266b1-bae7-44db-b999-f66a2f3fb589"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_f-v-CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947300359146","data":{"timestamp":" 947300359146"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000108_055559"," gameId":" b55266b1-bae7-44db-b999-f66a2f3fb589"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_D-B-P"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947300364871","data":{"timestamp":" 947300364871"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000108_055559"," gameId":" b55266b1-bae7-44db-b999-f66a2f3fb589"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_T-E-F"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947300369316","data":{"timestamp":" 947300369316"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000108_055559"," gameId":" b55266b1-bae7-44db-b999-f66a2f3fb589"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_E-F-T"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947300376606","data":{"timestamp":" 947300376606"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000108_055559"," gameId":" b55266b1-bae7-44db-b999-f66a2f3fb589"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947300384453","data":{"timestamp":" 947300384453"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000108_055559"," gameId":" b55266b1-bae7-44db-b999-f66a2f3fb589"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_R-H-A"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947300391694","data":{"timestamp":" 947300391694"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000108_055559"," gameId":" b55266b1-bae7-44db-b999-f66a2f3fb589"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_J-I-L"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947300398379","data":{"timestamp":" 947300398379"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000108_055559"," gameId":" b55266b1-bae7-44db-b999-f66a2f3fb589"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_T-I-J"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947300431239","data":{"timestamp":" 947300431239"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000108_055559"," gameId":" b55266b1-bae7-44db-b999-f66a2f3fb589"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_J_T-I-J"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}